## Bruno Vale Barbosa Eiterer

## Developer

Current interests include low-level embedded software, close to the hardware, as well as development of the hardware itself, matching the experience acquired during my career. I'm also interested in high-level software and app development in Python and C#.

#### Experiences

## 04/2018 - 02/2019

#### ASML - The Netherlands

Worldwide leader in lithography machines, used in integrated circuits manufacturing

Embedded Software Intern in the Motion Control team

- Implementation of an EtherCAT protocol prototype in C, both in Linux and Bare-Metal
- Implementation of test code in Python
- Successful integration of the protocol with existing code
- Development of getting started tutorials for new team members

# 01/2014 - 03/2018

## Embedded Systems Group - UFSC

#### Floripa-Sat project team member

Floripa-Sat is a project whose objective is developing the first Cubesat nanosatellite completely developed by students in Brazil

Intern in the Energy Power System

- Development of the firmware for the microcontroller and several other integrated circuits in C
  - Usage of communication protocols (I<sup>2</sup>C, SPI, UART, One-Wire)
  - Implementation of Maximum Power Point Tracking algorithms
  - Implementation of the task scheduler
- Development of the temperature control system for the nanosatellite batteries.
- Development of the voltage and current measurement circuits using amplifiers and ADCs
- Development of the test methodology and its documentation
- Implementation of buck and boost switch-mode converters
- Solar panels, switch-mode converters and load modeling using Matlab and Simscape
- Participation in the project hardware development
- All activities were executed under Scrum methodology

#### Education

03/2012 - 02/2019

## Electrical Engineering Bachelor

Federal University of Santa Catarina, Brazil

#### **Personal Information**

Bartolomeu de Gusmão Street, 371, Florianópolis, SC, Brazil

 $\square$  +55 48 99611-8470

☑ brunoeiterer@gmail.com

in brunoeiterer

• brunoeiterer

#### Languages

Brazilian Portuguese

Native

English

● ● ● Fluent

### Programming

С

● ● ● Advanced

Python

● O O Basic

C++

● O O Basic

Matlab

● O O Basic

C# .NET

● O O Basic

WPF

● O O Basic

#### Skills

Git

lacktriangledown lacktriangledown lacktriangledown

ClearCase

● O O Basic

MS Office

lacktriangledown lacktriangledown Intermediate

ĿŦĘX

● ● ○
Intermediate

Simulink

● O O Basic

Altium Designer

● O O Basic